in Moscow yes If a person
в Москве да Если человек на Красной
comes out on Red Square in yellow and blue yes they
площади выйдет в жёлтом и синем да о его
will arrest him Look how much it was
арестуют Посмотри сколько было потому
because the flag flag wait No not just
что флаг флаг подожди Нет не просто
just in yellow and
просто в жёлтом и
blue hello let's have a normal
синем привет давайте нормально
conversation come on come on just when we
пообщаемся давай давай просто когда мы
see the flag behind our backs it usually
видим флаг за спиной это обычно
starts
начинается
right away I don't right away I first communicate then
сразу я не сразу я сначала общаюсь потом
not right away come on come on Where are you from We are from
не сразу давайте давайте Вы откуда Мы с
Moscow cool How old are you
Москвы прикольно Сколько лет Вам
great
прекрасно
Yes how old are you as a girl we
Да как по сколько лет по дев нам
understand I myself live in California I am originally from
понял Я сам в Калифорнии живу родом из
Rostov but have been in California for 18 years already I am already
Ростова но уже 18 лет в Калифорнии Я уже
more American than Russian you can
больше американец чем русский можно так
say so California is great And
сказать Калифорния кра А мыслите на
what language do you think in I think in English already
каком языке мыслю на английском уже
yes zeros some everyday things Yes I am in
да нули бытовые какие-то вещи Да я на
English here in chat roulette then with
английском вот в чат рулетке то с
Russians and Ukrainians in Russian yes do you have children How old are
русскими и украинцами по-русски да дети
they are they 17 years old they are 8
есть Сколько им лет есть 17 лет есть 8
years old they are 4 years old and 1 year old Wow big
лет есть 4 года и 1 год Ух ты большая
family Well I have two
семья Да ну у меня две
wives you have already fulfilled the American
жены вы уже исполнили американскую
dream I am still fulfilling it is limitless
мечту исполняю ещё она безгранична
want to go to America You
хотите в Америку
should go to California in particular
Повали бы в Калифорнии в частности
to visit And what about you  attracts in
посетить А что вас привлекает в
America California Well Dream this is
Америке Калифорния Ну Мечта вот это
probably movies this is one and
наверно фильмы это раз а
where is it better in Russia or in California to
дте где лучше в России или в Калифорнии
live and I have not been to California And I would
жить а я не был в Калифорнии А я бы
say where are relatives probably Well in general yes the
сказал где родные наверное Ну вообще
standard of living is better in Russia or in
да уровень жизни луше в Росси или в
America therefore Well anyway Well according to
Амери поэто Ну всё равно Ну по
statistics Well in America it is good the middle
статистике Ну в Америке хорошо средний
class lives a little
класс получше живёт чуть
better Yeah I got it And what is good in Russia in Russia the
Угу понял А чем хорошо в России в России
service sector is very well developed the
сфера услуг развита очень хорошо сфера
service sector restaurants ba online banking
услуг рестораны ба олайн банкинг
restaurants Yes marketplaces
рестораны Да маркетплейсы
couriers marketplaces you are telling in
курьеры маркетплейсы ты рассказываешь в
this in America there is Amazon and you
этом в Америке есть Amazon и ты
are telling about some marketplaces
рассказываешь про какие-то маркетплейсы
in Russia Well well
в России Ну хорошо
widespread use and world fame
широкое пользование и всемир известность
And about convenience how long does it take for you to receive a parcel
А про удобство сколько вам прихо посыл
and
идт
sleep Are you kidding Well just for the sake of you
сна Ты прикалываешься Ну просто ради вы
ordered from Amazon how long does it take for you to receive a parcel on the
заказали с амазона сколько вам посылка в
same day on the same day Well that's
этот же день в этот же день Ну вот это
cool plus or minus also Maybe the
круто а плюс-минус также Может на
next day the next Yes that's a day to
следующий день на следующий Да это день
wait for the right thing they will bring it the
ждать нужная чтка те привезут на
next day that's
следущий день это
generally Well why is it not always the next day that you
вообще Ну почему не всегда на следующий
need to on
надо в
this looking at  what warehouses the goods
этот смотря на каких складах Товар
are with us this is all
находится у нас это всё сильно
developing very strongly That's exactly the service sector in
развивается Вот именно сферу услуг на
fact in the restaurant we
самом деле в ресторанчика у нас
serve Well I heard in the West
обслуживают Хорошо я услышал на западе
a little bit differently there still a little on No well
немного не так там всё-таки чуть на Не
here in the West in our restaurant
ну у нас на западе у нас в ресторанчика
then the products are
то продукты это
products Well by the way here in the USA I helped heard
продукты Ну кстати вот США я помо слышал
that the level of products is not very high
что уровень продуктов не очень высокий
Listen well I lived in Rostov and lived uh 18
Слушай ну я жил в Ростове и жил ээ 18
years in the USA then you
лет в США то такого как в Ростове у нас
won't find here in the USA what in Rostov And when in what
не найдёшь тут в США А когда в каком
Why Rostov Wait and in what year
Почему Ростов Подождите а в каком году
such in products as in Rostov And in
такого по продуктам как в Ростове А в
what year were you last in Rostov the
каком году вы последний раз в Ростове
last time 3 years ago just
были последний раз 3 года назад как раз
before before
перед до
I wonder well if if if in
сво интересно ну если если если у нас в
Russia we have sausage here it's not even called
России колбаса у нас она даже называется
sausage but look it says
не колбаса а посмотришь написано
sausage
колбасный
product no no I really saw straight
продукт не не я видел реально прямо
stories with rubber cucumbers in
истории с резиновыми огурцами в
America less than some
Америке меньше каких-то
look rubber cucumber What are you good but
смотри резиновый огурец Ты что хорошо а
OK with America it's clear no no some that
вот О'кей с Америкой понятно не не какие
is wait do you really think what they
то есть подожди ты реально думаешь что у
sell in our stores  rubber cucumbers
нас продают в магазинах резиновые огурцы
and we eat them No, it's just a convention
и мы их едим Да нет это же условность
Well, we only consume information
просто Ну мы же информацию потребляем
that is on the Internet Well,
только ту которая есть в интернете не Ну
how do you imagine a rubber
как ты представляешь себе резиновый
cucumber a rubber product means a
огурец продукто резиновый имеется в виду
low-quality one that is not a cucumber but
низкого качества который не огурец а
understand that it is conventional, don't look at us Well, how are
пойми что условно не смотри у нас ну как
they of low quality Here in Russia we have
их низкого качества Вот в России у нас
different cucumbers there are Bulgarian ones, they were
разные огурцы есть болгарские такие были
long Yes, there are short ones, here we have
длинные Да есть короткие такие у нас тут
dense ones, medium-dense ones, in
плотные средне плотные у нас в
California there are only about 20
Калифорнии только огурцов где-то 20
types of cucumbers there are small ones,
видов огурцов есть есть мелкие
spherical ones, whatever you want, you can
такие шарообразные что хочешь ту можно
take those I don't know and I wouldn't tell the boys
взять не знаю и пацанам я бы не сказал
at all I don't think about how much product
вообще не задумаюсь сколько продук
you buy and that's it you go to Rostov when you
покупаешь и всё идёшь в Ростове когда
were there you always count, look at what's
были там всегда считаешь смотришь что
there, how much it costs, and you go in and throw in these
там сколько стоит н зашёл накидал эти
fruits and products You throw in, I have
фрукты и продукты Закидываешь у меня
three refrigerators at home Yes, and two
дома три холодильника стоит Да и две
freezers, you Throw in
морозильных камеры ты Закидываешь это
all this, in short, there once a week we
всё короче там раз чтоб в д недели у нас
don't have that you know in Rostov like you
нету такого знаешь в Ростове типа ты там
go there and buy and go  bought here in short so
пошёл купил пошёл купил тут короче так
stocked up And what do you do as a
затарился А кем вы работаете
teacher at the university I
преподаватель в университете
teach anthropology how much do you get
антропологию преподаю сколько получаете
if Well not sig e by California standards not
если Ну не сиг э по меркам Калифорнии не
really a big salary it's 99,000
совсем большая зарплата это 99.000
dollars a month 9,300 if exactly in
долларов в месяц 9.300 если точно
Russian it comes out to 900 930,000 rubles
по-русски это получается 900 930 000 руб
a month how much do you spend on payments
в месяц сколько у вас на платежи уходит
from these Rene on payments What Well taxes
из этих Рене на платежи Какие Ну налоги
there taxes rent this is what
там налоги аренда это это то что на руки
I get in hand already this is after taxes and
получаю уже это после налогов и
insurance of all insurance 500 dollars
страховка всех страховка 500 долларов
medical
медицинская всё
covers everything well they said you have four children
покрывает ну сказали у вас четверо детей
wife So
жена Ну и
what five people 2500 and what do you give
что пять человек 2500 а что даёте вы
a two-story house like mine So what
двухэтажный дом типа у меня Ну и что
rent I teach
аренда преподаю
anthropology anthropology anthropology anthropology
антропологию антропологию антропологию
yeah Yeah
да Угу
I heard this word for the first time yeah No no
я первый раз услышали это слово да Не не
we know this And what is it I wonder
мы знаем это А что такое вот интересно
how people interpret what it is
как люди интерпретируют что это
Well if I'm not mistaken anthropology
А ну если я не ошибаюсь антропология -
is in my opinion when e bones are studied but no
это по-моему когда э кости изучают а нет
this is
это это
archeology all sorts not just bones But in
археология всякие не то что кости А
general all fossils anthropology  - this is
вообще всё ископаемое антропология - это
the study of man anthropos Well, yes, yes, that
изучение человека антропос Ну да да то
is, human populations And so on For
есть человеческих популяций И так дальше
example, you,
Вот вы например
uh, like in Bely What is your name My name is
ээ вот как в Белом Как вас зовут Меня
Dmitry Yes, Dmitry, you are not Russian No,
Дмитрий зовут Да Дмитрий ты не русский
I am Russian No, you are
Так нет я русский Нет ты не русский Я
not Russian As an anthropologist, I will say you are not Russian Yes, it is in
как антрополог скажу ты не русский да у
your passport Maybe I will explain to you
тебя в паспорте Может я тебе объясню
Look, where is my father Ukrainian, my
Смотри мой отец откуда украинец у меня
father That's it, I am telling you you are not a
отец Вот вот вот я же тебе говорю ты не
Russian anthropological type, not Russian
русский антропологический тип не русский
Where is he from Ukraine, exactly, he is from
откуда Из Украины он именно он с
Central Ukraine, Kirovograd
Центральной Украины Кировоградская
region Well, you see everything Yes, the thing is
область Ну всё видишь Да это дело в том
that the Russian anthropological type Well, not
что русский антропологический тип Ну не
like that I am immediately physiognomic and you,
такой Я по физиогномике сразу а ты
boy, are also not Russian Do you have someone from
парниша тоже не русский у тебя кто-то из
the Turks, where are the Turks Who are your
тюрков есть откуда тюрки Кто кто у тебя
parents My parents are Armenians Well, I am
родители Родители у меня армяне Ну вот я
saying something like that Yes, you are not
же говорю что-то такое да е ты не
Russian Well, it's not difficult I think so Well,
русский Ну это не сложно Я так думаю ну
yes, but the science itself is interesting And
да но сама наука интересная А преподаёте
what class do you teach Nasi Po You have two of you, both
какому классу наси по у тебя у тебя двое
mom and dad are Armenians Yes Or yes And
и мама и папа армяне да Или есть да А
where exactly are the Armenian type from Krasnodar
откуда именно типаж армян Краснодарский
or from Armenia
или из Армении
No, Abkhazian Armenians  Abkhazian And I can
нет абхазские армяне абхазские А я смо
because you don't look like those Armenians from
потому что ты не похож на таких армян из
Armenia Yes, you don't look like them, yes, Abkhazian Armenians,
Армении Да не похож да абхазские армяне
they have a separate type, yes, under the type Yes, it's
они отдельный тип имеют да под тип Да
called in anthropology, here it's
там называется в антропологии у нас это
called the Ochamchir subtype of Armenian
называется очамчирский подтип армянского
Oh yeah And where exactly from Abkhazia are you from?
Ай да А откуда именно вы из Абхазии
Good question My mother is an Abkhazian
родом Хороший вопрос У меня мама Абхаз
Armenian She was born in the Republic of Kazakhstan,
армянка Она родилась в
but she
рке а а
grew up Damn it Good
росла блин Хороший
question I don't remember I don't remember the city I
вопрос не помню я не вспомню город Я там
wasn't there either Yes, I saw the war with Yes, I
не был таже Да застала войну с Да
saw it, and that's why they moved
застала они из-за этого и переехали да
Yes, of course They left there I
Ясно Там уезжали
understood you two are not Russians I understood Well, you
понял вы двое не русских понял Ну вот
see, anthropology is such a good thing
видишь антропология - это такая хорошо
because here, like, everyone
потому что у нас как типа всех
is recorded as one nationality It seems
записывают в одну национальность Вроде
yes, those are those And when you, like an anthropo, you already
да те те А ты когда как антропо ты уже
look Well, while I was studying at school,
смотришь Ну вот я пока в школе учился
for me it was also all Russian there and
для меня тоже это было всё там русский и
so on Yes, here in Rostov And
так дальше Да вот у нас в Ростове А
now I understand now I even look at
теперь я понимаю теперь я смотрю даже
photographs of graduates from my class and they're
фотографии выпускников своего класса и
like, chick-chick-chick Well, copy it out of
такие чик-чик-чик А ну Списывай вот ради
interest, I say, says Yes, my mother is
интереса говорю говорит Да у меня мама
from Georgia, I  such Opa And so
из Грузии я такий Опа И так
on Yes in fact it is interesting blood is
дальше Да на самом деле интересно кровь
not found it can not be rewritten
не водится её так не перепишешь
yes And in what year did you move to the States
да А в ком году в Штаты переехали
18 years ago 18 years ago and on what
18 лет назад 18 лет назад а по какой
visa on the Student I completed
визе по Студенческой Я закончил в
five courses in Rostov and
Ростове пять курсов и на магистратуру
won a grant from the University for a master's degree Samantha
выиграл Грант университет Саманта
stayed here after her master's degree for
остался тут после магистратуры на
postgraduate study and after defending her dissertation Yes I
аспирантуру и после защиты диссертации
applied for
Да подался на
citizenship studied well
гражданство хорошо учились
Yes if I teach then it will not be here This is
Да если я преподаю то тут не будет Это в
possible in Russia according to You will be taken wherever
России можно быть по Тебя возьмут куда
you want but here everything is tough with this And what is it
хочешь а тут всё с этим жёстко А что там
with you there in short calm or with you there
у вас короче спокойно или у вас там
War is going on
Война идёт
uh territorially depending on where it is calm with us
ээ территориально смотря где у нас
And you again You in the city we are in
спокойно А вы ещё раз Вы городе мы в в
Mytishche MOPR Mos but in Mytishche something
Мытище МОПР Мос вот а в Мытище чтото ж
flew in there somewhere in Mytishche or nearby
прилетало там где-то в Мытище или рядом
Kolomna there were some arrivals no no
Коломна прилёты были какие-то нене
Kolomna further away a little tish Not further
Коломна подальше чу-чуть тищ Не подальше
Mytishchi No there were
Мытищах Нет не было
What does it mean what does the name
Что означает что означает название
Mytishche mean I always heard to me when
Мытище я всег какда слышал мне когда
there was a word Myt it was trade it
было слово Мыт это было торговля это
there was a trading point here the river
была торгов ная точка здесь река же
Yauza passes Yauza and Myt trade routes in
проходит Яуза Яуза и Мыт торговые пути в
general and here traders merchants were this
общем и здесь торговцы купцы были это
was a tax conditionally speaking Myt Yes this is a
налог был условно говоря Мыт Да это
tax that is why
налог та поэтому
Mytishchi Well yes that with the coat of arms of Ukraine sit and
Мытищ Ну да та с гербом Украины сидите
support yes Ukraine support
да поддерживаете да Украину поддерживай
Ukraine yes just for myself found out And
Украину да у просто для себя узнал А вы
what do you think who is to blame for this war Well
как считаете кто виноват в этой войне Ну
definitely not us Well who Well not specifically we are the
точно не мы Ну а кто Ну не конкретно мы
ones to blame for this war I think it is
вот кто виноват в этой войне Я думаю
hard to find one culprit here a
одного виноватого тут тяжело найти здесь
group of people from many
группа лиц с многих
sides who unleashed the conflict between the
сторон которые развязали конфликт между
Slavs Well and the Slavs themselves contributed to this
славянами Ну и славя сами этому
That is, did I understand correctly that someone
Вот то есть я правильно понял что кто-то
forced Putin to attack the
заставил Путина напасть на
Slavs I would say
славян я бы сказал
forced to the full
вынудили в полной
extent I acted differently a little I will Well it
мере я поступал иначе чуть-чуть буду Ну
turns out look Putin made it so that the
получается смотри Путин сделал так что
Slavs are killing the Slavs now so
славяне убивают славян сейчас так
braidan in
брайдан во
Why is Putin following the lead of some
Зачем Путин идт на поводу каких-то
puppeteers and making a civil
кукловодов и делает гражданскую
war protecting the state integrity of the
войну защита государственной целостности
country in what integrity it was whole
страны в чём целостность она была целая
now it is not whole after the beginning of its no longer
вот сейчас не целая после начала сво уже
whole Well it could have been worse In the sense
целое Ну могло бы быть хуже В смысле
it could have  it would be like well the troops of the North
могло бы быть это как ну войска Северно
Atlantic Alliance were approaching the
Атлантического Альянса приближались к
borders with Russia where they were approaching
границам с Россией где приближались
Well the entry Expanding the borders of NATO
Ну вступление Расширение границ НАТО
stop stop stop Well look there
стоп стоп стоп Ну смотри В Украине войск
were no NATO troops in Ukraine I am from America I know and in
НАТО не было Вот я из Америки Я знаю а в
Latvia in Latvia Lithuania and Estonia just
Латвии в Латвии Литве и Эстонии как раз
They were NATO troops Now also in
Они были войска НАТО Теперь ещё в
Finland NATO troops They just arrived that
Финляндии войска НАТО Они как раз приб
is Putin attacked where there were no
то есть Путин напал туда где никаких
NATO troops
войск НАТО и в помине не
Well where did you get the information that there
было Ну откуда вас информация что там не
were no troops there wax over because I work in an
было воск над потому что я работаю в
analytical center too Well let's say
аналитическом центре тоже Ну я допустим
in which analytical center you
в каком аналитическом центре это тебе
don't
знать не
need to know this migrant Well okay okay let it
надо мигрант Ну ладно ладно пусть
be your way And what do you
будет А вы как
think I think
считаете Я считаю
that Russia attacked Ukraine Yes and so the
что Россия напала на Украину Да и так
whole world thinks everything is clear here and for
весь мир считает тут всё чётко а по
what reason is your
какой причине ваше
opinion because look
мнение потому что смотри
uh the Nazi regime in the Kremlin is living out
ээ нацистский режим в Кремле доживает
its last days for it so that let's
свои последние дни ему для того
say it cannot show for
чтобы скажем он не может показать для
its for its population development Yes
своего для своего населения развития Да
it is robbing it completely has reached the end of its rope and the
он его грабит полностью дошёл до ручки и
only way it can Distract
единственное как он может Отвлечь
internal processes yes uh protests is
внутренние процессы да э протестные это
to start some kind of war yes
затеять какую-то войнушку да
imperialistic ti for for for
империалистическую ти для для для
expansion of territories that's all Well
расширения территорий вот и всё Ну
look Let's start with the last one
смотрите Давайте вот с последнего начнём
Let's not start with a little bit with the
Не давайте нач всё-таки с немножко с
Nazi
нацистского
regime just for fun How many
режима вот ради интереса Сколько в
mosques are there in Ukraine What do you think there is in
Украине мечетей Как вы думаете там ээ в
Crimea where there is a compact settlement of
Крыму где есть компактное поселение
Muslims historical And where in Crimea in Crimea
мусульман историче А где в Крыму в Крыму
are there mosques in Ukraine in Kyiv there are mosques
мечети в Украине есть в Киеве есть мечей
Yes the territory of Russia Now let's No
Да территория России Сейчас давайте Нет
this is the territory of Ukraine captured by
это территория Украины захваченная
Russia
Россией
Well even on Google maps Go to American
Ну даже на Google карты Зайдите Американ
what And what on Google map Go there it's
что И что на Google карте Зайди там это
not Russia look Okay let it be in
не Россия посмотри Хорошо пусть будет в
Crimea somewhere else well up to 10 there where
Крыму ещё где-то ну до 10 ту там там где
Muslims are there and what And where
мусульмане там и есть и что А откуда
will the mosque for example in Lviv if
будет мечеть например во Львове если там
non-Muslims live there And you think there are
не мусульмане живут А вы считаете во
no Muslims at all in Lviv Well not in
Львове нет мусульман вообще Ну нету в
such numbers Yes so that Muslims are
таком количестве Да чтобы мусульмане -
very now in my opinion they are even
это очень сейчас они по-моему даже
catching up with Christians already Well in Russia yes
догоняют уже христиан по Ну в России да
in Russia yes because in Russia now
в России да потому что в России сейчас
Come to Germany not in Russia look in
Прити на Германию не в России смотри в
Russia now yes there are more Muslims than
России сейчас да мусульман больше чем
Russians no yes that's for sure yes more
Русских нет да это однозначно да больше
good that's the
хорошо
question
вот вопрос
Yes  are you interested Why is Russia a
Да тебя заинтересовало Почему Россия -
Nazi state Yes about Yes I'll
это нацистское государство Да об Да
explain look because how many
объясняю смотри потому что сколько
nations live in Russia many many many
народов живёт в России много мно много
yes Tell me in which city there are non-
да Назови мне в каком городе есть не
Russian-language schools Russia closed
русскоязычные школы Россия закрыла в том
including Ukrainian-language schools that were
числе украиноязычный школы которые были
e private Ukrainian-language schools yes
э частные украинско язычные школы да
Russia closed 5 million Kazakhs live in Russia
Россия закрыла в России живёт 5 млн
Yes not a single Kazakhoil
казахов Да ни одной казахойл в России
about 7 million Ukrainians live in Russia not a single
живёт около 7 млн украинцев ни одной
Ukrainian-language school that is in Russia
украино язычной школы то есть в России
as a Nazi state prohibits
как нацистское государство запрещает
education in national languages Russia
обучение на национальных языках России
does not have My girlfriend and I have Ukraine Yes
нет Мы с моей девушкой нас Украины Да а
but we wanted to try national cuisine Well
вот хотели попробовать народную кухню Ну
Remember Bach's lard once again once again let's
Вспомни сало Баха ещё раз ещё раз давай
not about the girl Come on tell me why the
не про девушку Давай скажи почему
Nazi state Russian
нацистское государство Российская
Federation Yes prohibits education in the
Федерация Да запрещает обучение на
national languages of all these nations
национальных языках всех этих народов
666 nations that live You are wrong You are
666 народов которые живут Вы не правы Вы
wrong I recently saw an advertisement
не правы Я недавно видел рекламный ролик
in Chechnya they teach the Chechen language so that
в в Чечне преподают чеченский язык чтобы
Chechen develops yes look again
развивались чеченский да ещё раз смотри
no E the language is taught the same way look I'll
нет Э язык преподают так же как смотри
explain in  Bashkortostan teaches a lesson
объясню в Башкортостане преподают урок
twice a week Bashkort language yes And all
два раза в неделю башкорт язык да А все
other subjects are in Russian
остальные предметы идут на русском
mathematics in Russian and not in Chechen
математика на русском а не на чеченском
physics in Russian That
физика на русском То
is, the national language is assigned such a
есть национальному языку отводят такое э
property you know like this for
бы свойство знаешь как вот такое для
some rural conversations that is the
сельских разговоров каких-то то есть
Russian Federation Yes Nazi
Российская Федерация Да нацистское
state Yes where
государство Да где
is the Nazism of the Russian ethnic group in
ээ идёт нацизм русского этноса по
relation to everyone else in the same you
отношению ко всем остальным в том же вы
know yes and you had all these Nazi
знаете да и у вас эти все нацистские
marches Russian marches yes Russia for
марши русские марши были да Россия для
Russians Moscow for Muscovites Yes where
русских Москва для москвичей Да там где
you call it and this is the same in Russia uh
у вас называются и это же в России э
announcement we rent only to Slavs
объявление сдаём только славянам
mass I saw how a blogger blogger from
массовое Я видел как блогер блогерка из
Buryatia Yes told how in Voronezh in
Бурятии Да рассказывала как Воронеже в
Kursk she could not rent an apartment they
Курске не могла снять квартиру ей
told her like we rent only to
говорили типа не мы сдаём только
Slavs go to your country Where did
славянам едьте в свою страну Откуда
you come from Well this is
приехали Ну это же есть такое
true of course Well let's go now I then
правда безусловно Ну давайте теперь я то
Wait wait then Russia is a Nazi
Подожди подожди то Россия нацистское
state so no Why not I explain
государство так нет Почему нет объясняю
My girlfriend and I decided to eat
Мы с моей девушкой решили покушать
Ukrainian cuisine we came to a restaurant in the
украинскую кухню мы пришли в ресторан в
center of Moscow called  Korchma, there are a
центре Москвы называется Корчма э там
lot of posters hanging there. Well, that is,
висит очень много плакатов Ну то есть
the interior is made directly under the
сделан интерьер непосредственно под на
Ukrainian language, Ukrainian songs are played
украинском языке играют украинские песни
in the center of Moscow, people come there and
в центре Москвы туда приходит люди
eat calmly,
спокойно кушают
and its super in the Third Reich. Ill tell you more,
а супер в третьем рейхе Я тебе больше
in the Third Reich during Hitlers time, there
скажу в третьем рейке во время Гитлера
were restaurants like Cyno, yes, with
Да были ресторанчики типа цино сная да с
Jewish cuisine, music was playing there. Yes, and the
Еврейской кухней там музыка играла Да а
Jews were exterminated,
еврее уничтожали
and there was a restaurant with Jewish cuisine, and a
а ресторан Еврейской кухни был приходила
woman came and dined there. And what else will I
ги Тапа там обедала И что дальше
tell you? Youre talking about Moscow for
расскажу Вот вы говорите про Москва для
Russia, for Russians. Moscow for Muscovites.
России для русских Москва для москвичей
People were imprisoned for this. Bright
за это сажали людей яркие
examples of media personalities, who were
примеры медийных личностей кого
imprisoned for this, but not for this. They
тиса тика не за это посадили тика
imprisoned for this. But for killing people, no, for
посадили За то за убийство людей нет за
killing people,
убийство людей
but this is no longer the case. Tesak was imprisoned for this.
по это уже не Тесака не за это посадили
Tesak was imprisoned for many other things. If you are
Тесака посадили За многое другое Если вы
in Moscow and say that there are some
в Москве и сказать что там ну какие-то
anti-Uranian slogans there. Well, yes, if you
антиуран ские лозунги Ну да если с
connect them with the people, like killing, there are
народом связывать типа убивать там вот
such bad things there. Look, Ill tell you more. In
такие плохие вещи смотри больше скажу в
Moscow, yes. If a person
Москве да Если человек на Красной
goes out on Red Square in blue, yes, they
площади выйдет в и синем да о его
will arrest him.  Look how much was beno
арестуют Посмотри сколько было бено
because the flag flag wait No not
потому что флаг флаг подожди Нет не
just just in yellow and blue just in
просто просто в жёлтом и синем просто в
yellow and blue This is the flag of Kazakhstan
жёлтом и синем Это флаг Казахстана
yellow and blue look there is a guy from
жёлтый и синий посмотри есть парень из
Tuva The Republic of Tuva is part of the
из тывы Республика Тыва в составе
Russian Federation It also has a yellow and
Российской Федерации Тоже имеет жёлтый и
blue flag Yes and he was indignant that
синий флаг Да вот и он возмущался что
he Yes on Red Square he was arrested for this
ему Да на Красной площади его за это
more than that if Why did you
арестова больше того если Почему у вас
arrest people who
арестовывали людей которые
brought flowers to the monument to Lasya Ukrainka
к памятнику Ласи Украинки приносили
we were not arrested they were arrested
цветы нас не арестовали арестовали
look google google detention
посмотри загугли загугли
what no no google really
задержание что нет нет загугли реально
look there is a video there police Yes the police are
посмотри там видео полиция Да полиция
arresting people who brought to
арестовывают людей которые приносили на
in the center of Moscow there is a painted shopping center for
в центре Москвы стоит торговый центр
the first time look come on like this look
впер смотри давай так е раз вот смотри у
you have a colleague sitting Let him open his
тебя сидит коллега Пусть сейчас откроет
phone now and look at the monument
телефон и посмотри памятник
flowers were arrested here on Come on write
цветы арестовали вот на Давай напиши
arrested for flowers on the monument to class
арестовали за цветы на памятник класе
Ukrainka
Украинке
Let's detain in memory of the Ukrainian authorities
Давай задержали на памят властям Украины
not Lesya Ukrainka is a poetess like that
не Леся Украинка поэтесса такая Да
Yes in Moscow yes at the monument to Lasya
вот в Москве да у памятника Ласи
Ukrainka in Moscow the snares detained two
Украинки в Москве силки задержали двух
people who  Brought flowers to the memorial take
человек которые Принесли к мемориалу
in Google the monument to Lasya
цветы возьми в Гугле памятник Ласи
Ukrainka detained they were
Украинки задержали их
arrested Where Where Where Where Where
арестовали Куда Куда Куда Куда
[music]
[музыка]
Where A where switched
Куда А куда переключился
and a beautiful roast yes Russia is a Nazi
а красивая прожарка да Россия нацистское
state Russia is a Nazi
государство Россия нацистское
state that there is a restaurant
государство то что там есть ресторан в
where borscht is served Yes this does not mean
котором борщ подают Да это не значит
that Russia is not There is a Nazi
что Россия не Есть нацистское
state So what subscribe to my
государство Ну и что подпишись на мий
Instagram I don't know what it is for
Instagram Я не знаю для чего це тоб Для
Why should you watch Of A for you
чего тоб там дивитись на Оф А для тебе
one or three
онд або три
But you try me and I will say Wow in
Але ты тримае мене и я буду казати Вау в
me there are a bunch of fouls and in me there will be a
мене там Купа фолов и в мене буде
cool mood so that you make a new spin
класний настр щоб робите нове крути
video letter on my Instagram popk Andriy Oh
видео пись на мий инстагра попк Андрий О
so come on
так давай
chick a
ячка а